Guide to the Raymond C. Battalio and John B. Van Huyck Papers, 1949-2014, bulk 1972-2014 RL.11714
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Experiments, 1986-2013
  - Other Experiments and Related Materials, 1985-2013
    - Other Experiments and Related Materials Electronic Files, 1985-2009; 82,943 files; approximately 10.1 gigabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
      RL11714-FL3-0744 contains a demo of a Bayesian learning experiment that can be played by a single individual against a simulated opponent using DOSBox. This experiment comes from the Economic Science Laboratory at the University of Arizona and is copyrighted 1991-1993.
    - PG3: Crowding Out, 2008 (Box 59)
      Notes on experiments on crowding out of public goods.
    - PRBMAT2, 1994; 2 folders (Box 59)
      Participant instructions, response sheets, and experiment data.
    - PRBMAT2 Electronic Files, 1992-1996; 603 files; approximately 22 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - Pubseq, undated; 3 folders (Box 60)
    - Pubseq Electronic Files, 1995-1997; 28 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - Pubseq2 Electronic Files, 1996; 10 files; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - Pubseq3 Electronic Files, 1995-1996; 45 files; approximately 3 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
      Text and dataset files.
    - Rat Coordination, 1990 and undated; 2 folders (Box 60)
      Notes and experiment data from experiments on adaptive behavior in rats.
    - Rationality of Altruism, 1999 (Box 60)
    - Replicator Dynamics (EV1), 1990-1991; 3 folders (Box 60)
    - Reporting Sheet Examples, undated (Box 64)
    - Response Booklets, undated; 10 folders (Box 65)
      For unlabeled experiment(s).
    - Restaurant Choosing Game, undated (Box 60)
    - Risk Dominance, 1994 (Box 60)
    - Risk Dominance Electronic Files, 1994; 4 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 71, Disk RL11714-FL3-0619, Disk RL11714-FL3-0620)
    - RL1, 2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box 60)
    - RL1 Electronic Files, 2000-2001; 126 files; approximately 13 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 76, Optical-disc RL11714-OP-0059)
    - ROS, undated; 2 folders (Box 60)
    - ROS Electronic Files, 2000-2001; 92 files; approximately 9 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006, Box 76, Optical-disc RL11714-OP-0040)
    - ROS1, undated (Box 60)
    - RPS, 1994-1995; 3 folders (Box 60)
    - RPS Electronic Files, 1991-1995; 595 files; approximately 25 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - Sample Game Materials, 1995 (Box 64)
    - Sample Payoff Table Experiment Forms, undated (Box 64)
    - SEQAB, undated (Box 60)
    - SEQBA, undated; 2 folders (Box 60)
    - SEQSIM, 1995-1996 and undated; 7 folders (Box 60)
    - SEQSIM Electronic Files, 1994-1997; 904 files; approximately 22 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - SEQSIM2, 1996 (Box 61)
    - SEQSIM2 Electronic Files, 1994-1996; 309 files; approximately 8 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - SEQSIM3, 1996 and undated; 2 folders (Box 61)
    - SEQSIM3 Electronic Files, 1994-1996; 325 files; approximately 11 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0006)
    - Sequential Equilibrium, 1986-1996; 2 folders (Box 61)
      Notes and statistical analyses.
    - SIMAB, undated (Box 61)
    - SIMBA, undated; 2 folders (Box 61)
    - Software Installation Disks, 1990-2008 (Box 75, Box 80, Box 81)
      The largest amount are for Ecco, Mathematica, Microsoft Office, Parition Magic, Quattro Pro, SAS, TextBridge, Visual Studio, VS.NET, Windows, and Word Perfect; an inventory is available for request from Research Services.
    - Surveys (1-24 of 46), 2009-2012; 24 folders (Box 61)
      Anonymized surveys of participant demographic information.
    - Surveys (25-46 of 46), 2012-2013; 22 folders (Box 62)
    - T-Death, undated (Box 62)
    - Template Forms, 1987 (Box 64)
    - Two Pot One Chip, 1989; 2 folders (Box 62)
    - Unlabeled Response Form (1-5 of 37), 1998 and undated; 5 folders (Box 62)
      From unidentified experiments.
    - Unlabeled Response Forms (6-26 of 37), 1998-2000 and undated; 21 folders (Box 63)
    - Unlabeled Response Forms (27-37 of 37), 1998-2001 and undated; 11 folders (Box 64)
    - Van Huyck: Instructions, undated (Box 64)
      For unlabeled experiment.
    - Van Huyck: Dominant Instructions, undated (Box 64)
    - Van Huyck: Insurance Instructions, undated (Box 64)
    - Van Huyck: Median Instructions, undated (Box 64)
    - Van Huyck: Neg. Instructions, undated (Box 64)
    - Van Huyck: Paired with Same Person, undated (Box 64)
      Instructions for unlabeled experiment.
    - Van Huyck: Prediction Instructions, undated (Box 64)
    - Van Huyck: Predictions, undated (Box 64)
    - Van Huyck: Questions, undated (Box 64)
      Response form for unlabeled experiment.
    - Van Huyck: Reporting Sheets, undated (Box 64)
    - Van Huyck: Return to No Neg. Instructions, undated (Box 64)
    - Van Huyck: Table, undated (Box 64)
  - Uncategorized Electronic Files, 1986-2010
    Eletronic files from experiments that could not be categorized, either due to lack of identifiers or the disk containing files related to multiple/all experiment types.
    - Experiment Files from Computer Hard Disks and USB Drives, 1999-2007; 55,322 files; approximately 5.8 gigabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0007)
      Text, executable, image, dataset, spreadsheet, audio, backup, and database files; zipped folders.
    - Experiment Files from Digital Media, 1986-2003; 118,010 files; approximately 11 gigabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0007, Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0008)
      Text, executable, dataset, image, spreadsheet, audio, backup, font, presentation, and database files; zipped folders.
    - Quarter-Inch Cartridges, 1993-1995
      The contents of these cartridges are unknown due to format but they are labeled.
      - M66, D: Data/Word, 1993 (Box 79, Tape RL11714-QIC-0001)
      - M66, Full D:, 1995 (Box 79, Tape RL11714-QIC-0005)
      - Ma66, Full C: and C:\Windows, 1995 (Box 79, Tape RL11714-QIC-0002)
      - Ma66, Full D: and E:, 1995 (Box 79, Tape RL11714-QIC-0003)
      - Post OS2 v.3.0, Full C:, 1994 (Box 79, Tape RL11714-QIC-0004)
- Academia, 1975-2013
  Material such as correspondence, university administrative files, student advising files, and teaching material that relate to Battalio and Huyck's careers as academic economists, plus academic coursework and personal material for Van Huyck. Organized into four subseries: Department and University Business, Supervised Dissertations and Theses, Teaching, and Van Huyck Coursework and Personal Items.
  - Department and University Business, 1984-2012
    Includes administrative files, such as for department and university committee service. The largest file is on the Economics Research Laboratory (ERL), which Battalio and Van Huyck founded in 1997 and used to conduct experiments. Arranged alphabetically.
    - Academic Program Standards Committee, 1994-1997 (Box 15)
      Van Huyck served on Committee.
    - Administrative Documents, undated (Box 15)
      Unlabeled administrative material.
    - Association of Former Students Distinguished Achievement Awards, 1987 (Box 15)
      Memos.
    - Battalio, 1996-1999; 2 folders (Box 15)
      Unsorted professional and personal material on routine business.
    - Battalio: CV, 2000-2002 (Box 15)
    - Battalio: Research Reporting, 2000 (Box 15)
      Reports on faculty professional activity.
    - Brown Foundation Student Award, 1995 (Box 15)
      Material on committee service.
    - Bus Routes and Parking, undated (Box 15)
    - Bush Museum, undated; 2 folders (Box 15)
      George H. W. Bush Presidential Library in College Station.
    - Call Agenda, undated (Box 15)
      Template for notes on phone call.
    - Call Log, 1991-1992 (Box 15)
      Notes on phone calls.
    - Communication Log, 1988-1995; 3 folders (Box 15)
      Call logs with dates and purpose(s) of communication.
    - CS Housing, 2000 (Box 15)
      Housing near TAMU.
    - Dean Fallon Lecture Award, 1995 (Box 15)
    - Department and University Business Electronic Files, 1992-2004; 6,283 files; approximately 1.4 gigabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0009)
      Personnel restriction until 2081.
      Text, image, spreadsheet, and database files; zipped folders.
    - Department Bylaws, 1997 (Box 15)
    - Department Files, 1990-1995 and undated; 4 folders (Box 15)
      Routine business.
    - Economic Humor, 1990-1993 (Box 15)
      Jokes and comic strips.
    - Economic Science Forum, 1996 (Box 15)
      Meeting notes.
    - Economics Major, 1986 (Box 15)
      Undergraduate economics major.
    - Economics Research Lab (ERL), 1996-2009; 6 folders (Box 15)
      Material on managing the lab.
    - Economics Research Lab (ERL) Electronic Files, 1998-2003; 332 files; approximately 16 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0009, Box 77, Optical-disc RL11714-OP-0172)
      Text, executable, and database files; zipped folders.
    - Electronic Working Papers, 1996 (Box 15)
      Material on establishing an electronic working paper series.
    - External Review, 1990-2008 and undated; 4 folders (Box 15)
      Departmental reviews.
    - Faculty Development Leave, 1994-2010; 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Filing Systems No.9, 1984-1992 (Box 16)
      Notes on filing methods.
    - Graduate Instruction Committee, 1995-2000; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Graduate Student Policy, 1996 (Box 16)
    - Gregory Award, 1990 (Box 16)
    - Grossman Memorial, 2004 (Box 16)
      Program and other material for memorial service in memory of Van Huyck's doctoral advisor, Herschel Grossman.
    - GSIA Postdoctoral Fellowship, 1988 (Box 16)
      Call for nominations.
    - Hardware, 2000 (Box 16)
      Material on computer hardware.
    - Head Search Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 16)
      Van Huyck served on committee searching for department head.
    - Hiring, 2001 (Box 16)
      Battalio served on hiring committee.
    - Hiring: Interview Notes, 2008 (Box 16)
      Van Huyck's notes on interviews.
    - Hoover Fellowship, 1988-1992 (Box 16)
      Calls for applications.
    - Instructional Development Grant, 1992 (Box 16)
    - Internal Grants, 2007-2008 (Box 16)
    - Irving Fisher's Machine, undated (Box 16)
      Student competition to build a replica of Fisher's machine, a hydraulic machine for computing equilibrium prices.
    - Liberal Arts Retreat (TAES), 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 16)
      Interdisciplinary faculty retreat.
    - Mailing Lists, 1992-1996 (Box 16)
    - Manuals, undated (Box 16)
      Various manuals for office equipment.
    - Meeting Agenda, undated (Box 16)
      Template for meeting agenda and notes.
    - Microeconomics Lecture Notes, undated (Box 16)
      Copies of lecture notes from other economists.
    - Miscellaneous Handouts, undated (Box 16)
      Material on evaluating mathematics programs in Texas public schools.
    - Olin Fellowship, 1988 (Box 16)
      Call for applications.
    - PhD Dissertation Manual, undated (Box 16)
    - PhD Program, 1992 (Box 16)
      Possible revisions to PhD program.
    - Press Clippings, undated; 2 folders (Box 16)
      Newspaper clippings kept by Battalio.
    - Recruiting, 1992; 2002; 2 folders (Box 16)
      Graduate student recruiting.
    - Research Agenda, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Research and Teaching Planner, 1988-1992; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Research Reports TAMU Economics Laboratory, 1994 (Box 16)
      Material on printing reports.
    - Rex Grey Professorship, 2012 (Box 16)
      Van Huyck's endowed professorship.
    - Science Workshop, 1994 (Box 16)
      Faculty workshops and seminars.
    - Social Science Citation Index, 1998 (Box 16)
      Tracking paper citations.
    - Software Licenses, 1995-2006 (Box 16)
    - TAMU Engineering Experiment Station (TEES) Capabilities Book, 1987 (Box 16)
      Research team at TAMU.
    - Van Huyck: CV, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Van Huyck: Faculty Summary, 2011 (Box 16)
      Summaries of faculty professional activities.
    - Van Huyck: Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 16)
    - Van Huyck: Personal Stationery, undated (Box 16)
    - Van Huyck: TAMU Offer, 2000 and undated (Box 16)
      Material and correspondence on Van Huyck's position at TAMU.
    - Web Transactions, 2000 (Box 16)
      Receipts for research materials.
  - Supervised Dissertations and Theses, 1984-2009
    Includes copies and drafts of dissertations and theses, supporting research material, and correspondence. Arranged alphabetically by last name.
    - Aughinbaugh, Alison, 1992-1993 (Box 16)
    - Bailie, Christine (DeBerry), 1992 (Box 16)
    - Chen, Ho-Chyuan, undated (Box 16)
    - Cho, Jung-Hun, 2005-2006 (Box 16)
    - Cook, Joe, 1992-1994 (Box 17)
    - Dickerson, Matt, 1994 (Box 17)
    - Gilsoul, Raymond, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Hung, Tingwen, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Javier, Jaime, 1997 (Box 17)
    - Johnson, Adrea, 1997 (Box 17)
    - Kim, Geumsoo, 1991 (Box 17)
    - Koc, Sevket, 2002 (Box 17)
    - Komain, 1987 and undated; 3 folders (Box 17)
    - Kogut, Carl A., 1984 (Box 17)
    - Lee, Sang-Yong (Tom), 1994-1999; 3 folders (Box 17)
    - Linden, Mary Frances, 1993-1994 (Box 17)
    - Laccasen, R., 2003; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Malaga, Jaime, 1993-1994 (Box 17)
    - Manning, Robert, 2002 (Box 17)
    - Mathur, Sondip, 1991 (Box 17)
    - McKinney, C. Nicholas, 2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Nordt, Daniel, 2007-2009; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - O'Donnell, Sean, 1994-1995 (Box 17)
    - O'Donnell, Sean Electronic Files, 1995; 8 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0009, Box 75, Disk RL11714-FL3-1180)
    - Oyarzun, Carlos, 2007-2008 (Box 17)
    - Quigley, Matthew S., 1996 (Box 17)
    - Radcliff, Tiffany, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Rai, Brandy, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Rankin, Frederick William, 1995-1996; 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Robb, Daniel, 2000 (Box 18)
    - Sarin, Rajiv, 1994 (Box 18)
    - Scott, Jason, undated (Box 18)
    - Seely, Beth, 1992-1996; 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Song, Guobin, 1996 (Box 18)
    - Supervised Theses and Dissertations Electronic Files, 1984-2001; 27,926 files; approximately 1.7 gigabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0009)
      Text, dataset, executable, image, audio, backup, and spreadsheet files; zipped folders; the largest amount of files are for Bill Rankin and Beth Seely.
    - Thibaud, Catherine, 1993 (Box 18)
    - Umaraliev, Abdugaffor, 2005 (Box 18)
    - Wade, Chad, 2003-2006 and undated; 6 folders (Box 18)
    - Walters, Mary, 1990-1992; 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Watugala, Megha, 2006-2008 (Box 18)
    - Weber, Roberto (1-2 of 4), 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Weber, Roberto (3-4 of 4), undated; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Wildenthal, John, 1993-2001; 4 folders (Box 19)
    - Yang, Wang, 1997 (Box 19)
  - Teaching, 1981-2013
    Includes syllabi, lecture notes and slides, handouts, assignments, exams, and readings. The largest files are for courses on behavioral game theory, experimental economics, and macroeconomics. Arranged alphabetically by course code or title.
    - Advanced Macroeconomics--Monetary and Fiscal Policy (Van Huyck), 1990; 2 folders (Box 19)
      Syllabus and lecture notes.
    - Advanced Theory (Ec 201; Sobel), 1991 (Box 19)
      Course taught by another faculty member.
    - Agricultural Economics Prelims, 1988 (Box 19)
      Field exams.
    - Behavioral and Experimental Economics Field Exam, undated (Box 19)
      Field exam and sample responses.
    - Classroom Experiment (Holt), undated (Box 19)
      Material for classroom experiments designed by Charles Holt.
    - CommLab Games, 1999 (Box 19)
      Material for classroom experiments.
    - Course Syllabi, undated (Box 19)
      Copies of course syllabi from other economists kept by Van Huyck.
    - Ec 410: Macroeconomics (Van Huyck), 1983-2010; 16 folders (Box 19)
      Syllabi, notes, lecture slides, exams, and other course material.
    - Ec 440: Experimental Economics (Battalio), 1996; 14 folders (Box 20)
      Notes and material for in-class experiments.
    - Ec 440: Experimental Economics (Battalio) Electronic Files, 16 files; approximately 4 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0009)
    - Ec 459: Games and Economic Behavior (Van Huyck), 2001-2009 and undated; 8 folders (Box 20)
      Notes, lecture slides, handouts, and other course material.
    - Ec 485: Genetic Algorithms, 1990 (Box 20)
      Syllabus and presentation material.
    - Ec 611: Macroeconomic Theory (Van Huyck), 1988-1989; 8 folders (Box 20)
      Syllabi, exams, notes, and other course material.
    - Ec 636: Macroeconomic Theory (Van Huyck), 1986-1988; 9 folders (Box 20)
    - Ec 659: Behavioral Game Theory/Advanced Topics in Game Theory (Van Huyck), 1993-2008; undated; 41 folders (Box 21)
      Syllabi, lecture notes and slides, assignments, exams, and readings.
    - Ec 689: Special Topics in Game Theory (Van Huyck), 1990 (Box 21)
      Syllabus.
    - Game Theory, 1992-1997; undated; 10 folders (Box 22)
      Lecture notes and readings.
    - Game Theory (Roth), 1997; 2 folders (Box 22)
      Lecture notes and readings for course based on materials by Alvin Roth.
    - Game Theory (Ray's Notes), undated; 2 folders (Box 22)
      Copies of Battalio's notes on teaching game theory.
    - Games and Economic Behavior (Van Huyck), 1992; 3 folders (Box 22)
      Lecture notes and other course material.
    - How to Think Like a Computer Scientist, undated; 2 folders (Box 22)
      Copy of book used in classes.
    - Introduction to Macroeconomics (Van Huyck), 1990-1991 and undated; 19 folders (Box 23)
      Lecture notes and slides and other course material.
    - Lecture Notes, undated; 2 folders (Box 23)
      Lecture notes on topics in game theory.
    - Lecture Slides, undated; 2 folders (Box 23)
      Unlabeled by Van Huyck.
    - Macroeconomics Bibliography, undated (Box 23)
      Readings lists for macroeconomics courses taught by other economists.
    - Macroeconomics Lecture Notes (Van Huyck), 1988 and undated; 4 folders (Box 23)
      Lecture notes.
    - Macroeconomics Prelim, 1991 (Box 23)
      Material for macroeconomics PhD field exam.
    - Maskin's Game, undated (Box 23)
      Material for in-class game by Eric Maskin.
    - Other Syllabus, 1988 (Box 23)
      Syllabi from other economists.
    - Sargent Lecture Notes, undated; 2 folders (Box 23)
      Van Huyck's lecture notes based on Thomas Sargent's work.
    - Study Group, 1991 (Box 23)
      Notes on topics in game theory.
    - Teaching Electronic Files, 1990-2013; 6,322 files; approximately 1.9 gigabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0009)
      Text, image, presentation, spreadsheet, dataset, executable, and audio files; zipped folders.
    - Teaching Evaluations, 1987-2012; 3 folders (Box 23)
      Van Huyck's teaching evaluations.
    - Teaching Tips, 1981-1994 (Box 24)
      Notes and handouts on teaching.
    - Teaching Materials, 1995 and undated; 3 folders (Box 24)
      Syllabi and other unsorted course material from Van Huyck.
    - Theory Field Exam, 1995-2007 and undated (Box 24)
      Material for economic theory PhD field exam.
    - Time Inconsistency of Optimal Plans due to Forward Looking Expectations, undated (Box 24)
    - Z-tree Experimenter's Manual, 2000 (Box 24)
      Used in classes.
  - Van Huyck Coursework and Personal Items, 1975-2009
    Includes notebooks and term papers from Van Huyck's undergraduate and graduate coursework, plus any personal material. Arranged alphabetically.
    - A Stochastic Helicopter Money Model, undated (Box 24)
      Term paper.
    - Abstracts of Some Recent Research on Majority Voting, undated (Box 24)
    - An Overview of the Theory of Consistent Aggregation, undated (Box 24)
      Term paper; first in graduate school.
    - CitiCorp Fellowship, 1984 (Box 24)
      Application.
    - Consequences of Arrow's Impossibility Theorem, 1982; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Dissertation Proposal, 1984 (Box 24)
      Draft with notes and comments.
    - Dissertation Support, 1984 (Box 24)
      Funding.
    - Faculty Relations, 1985 (Box 24)
      Notes on conversations with faculty.
    - Game Materials, undated (Box 25)
      Notecards and poker chips used in games.
    - Granger Tests of Cost-Push Theories of Inflation, undated; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Guest Lecture on Granger Causality, 1982 (Box 24)
      Lecture notes for unknown class.
    - Instructions for PhD, 1986 (Box 24)
      Procedure for submitting dissertation.
    - Notebook, undated (Box 24)
      Notes on consumer behavior.
    - Notebooks: Applied Mathematics 165, 1980 (Box 24)
    - Notebooks: Consumer Surplus, undated (Box 24)
    - Notebooks: Ec 158, 1980 (Box 24)
      Class notes on the history of economic thought.
    - Notebooks: Ec 206, 1981; 2 folders (Box 24)
      Class notes on microeconomic theory.
    - Notebooks: Ec 208, undated (Box 24)
      Class notes on econometrics and macroeconomics.
    - Notebooks: Ec 280, 1981 (Box 24)
      Class notes on programming problems and game theory.
    - Notebooks: Econometrics, 1981-1983 and undated; 4 folders (Box 24)
    - Notebooks: Granger Causality, undated (Box 24)
    - Notebooks: Growth, 1981 (Box 24)
    - Notebooks: Henderson paper, undated (Box 24)
      Class notes on bargaining problems.
    - Notebooks: International Trade, 1981 (Box 24)
    - Notebooks: Macroeconomic Policy, 1978 (Box 24)
    - Notebooks: Mathematics for Economists, 1980 (Box 24)
    - Notebooks: Monetary Economics, 1981 (Box 24)
    - Notebooks: Problem Sets, undated (Box 25)
    - Notebooks: Thesis Ideas, undated (Box 25)
      Notes on possible thesis topics.
    - Notebooks: Urban Public Finance, 1982 (Box 25)
    - Notebooks: Welfare Economics, 1982 (Box 25)
    - Notes to Myself, 1984-1985 (Box 25)
      Notes on economic ideas and issues.
    - Personal Sketchbook, 1975 and undated (Box 25)
    - Public Finance, Social Welfare Functions, and Income Redistribution, undated (Box 25)
    - Research Proposal, 1982 (Box 25)
    - Sloan Fellowship, 1984 (Box 25)
      Materials for Fellowship application.
    - Some Evidence of a Monetary Business Cycle, 1983 (Box 25)
    - Thesis Proposal, 1982; 2 folders (Box 25)
      Draft thesis proposals.
    - Van Huyck Coursework and Personal Items Electronic Files, 1988-2009; 22,682 files; approximately 12.9 gigabytes. (Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0008, Digital-materials RL11714-SET-0010)
      Text, image, audio, aggregate, executable, spreadsheet, database, and dataset files; zipped folders; includes no coursework but a large amount of family material.
    - Ventilation File, 1984 (Box 25)
      Notes on research topics.
- Uncategorized Microcassettes, 1994 and undated
  Access note. Series contains fragile audio formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
  The contents of these microcassettes are unknown due to unclear/no labeling and format.
  - Original Microcassette, Hey, Andreoni, Brock, Deveckeve, Samuelson, Durlauf and Rust, undated (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-MCS-0007)
  - Original Microcassette, Notes, undated (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-MCS-0011)
  - Original Microcassette, Palfrey's Talk, undated (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-MCS-0006)
  - Original Microcassette, 1994 (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-MCS-0001)
  - Original Microcassette, 1994 (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-MCS-0003)
  - Original Microcassette, undated (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-MCS-0004)
  - Original Microcassette, undated (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-MCS-0005)
  - Original Microcassette, undated (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-MCS-0008)
  - Original Microcassette, undated (Box 79, Audio-cassette RL11714-MCS-0009)